{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Enterwell Quiz",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "3 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "3 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Enterwell Quiz 3",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "3 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "3 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "5 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "5 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "6 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "6 Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "name": "Enterwell Quiz 4",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "5 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "5 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "6 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "6 Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "name": "Enterwell Quiz 6",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "6 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "6 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "5 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "5 Ada Lovelace"
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "6 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
          "answer": "6 Ada Lovelace"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "2 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "2Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "3 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "3 Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "4 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "4 Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "5 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "5 Ada Lovelace"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "6 Who was the English mathematician and writer widely considered as the worldq's first computer programmer for her work on Charles Babbage's proposed mechanical general-purpose computer, the Analytical Engine?",
      "answer": "6 Ada Lovelace"
    }
  ]
}
